怎么了
What's going on?
我的眼睛有点痒
Well, my eye is a little itchy.
我的也是
Uh, mine too. Yeah.
你的眼睛好红喔  你应该去看我的眼科医生
Wow, it's really red. You should go see my eye doctor.
理查  我才不要找你的前男友看眼睛
Richard? I'm not gonna go see your ex-boyfriend.
理查  一天到晚理查个没完
Richard, that's all I ever hear. Richard, Richard, Richard.
打从我们开始约会以后  我想我只提过两次他的名字
Since we've been going out, I think I've mentioned his name twice.
那好  理查  理查
Okay. So Richard, Richard.
不是理查啦  我新找的眼科医生  他很棒
It's not Richard, okay? It's this new guy. He's really good.
抱歉  我不去看眼科医生
I'm sorry. I'm not going to an eye doctor.
天啊  老毛病又犯了  什么
Oh, God. Here we go. What?
每次只要提到眼睛这档事  她马上就避之唯恐不及
Any time anything comes close to touching her eye or anyone else's.she, like, freaks out.
注意看
Watch.
罗斯  你别闹了
Ross, come on.
好  我对我的眼睛有怪癖  麻烦别再讨论了  行吗
All right, fine. I have a weird thing with my eye. Can we not talk about it please?
好吧
All right.
瑞秋  还记得有首很棒的歌
Hey, Rach. You know that great song?
" 我"  我自己和( " 我" 和" 眼睛" 同音）
Um, "Me, myself and eye."
摩妮卡  别闹啦
Aah! Monica. Come on.
有没有人想吃午餐  有意愿的请说
Does anyone wanna get some lunch? All those in favor, say "eye."
罗斯  拜托  别闹了啦
Ross, stop it. Come on.
我有多喜欢《国王与我》
How much did I love The King and "Eye."
钱德
Chandler.
我也是
Me too, me too.
够了  别玩了
Just stop it. That's enough. Come on.
你还好吧  对  我太兴奋了  戳到了
You okay there, man? Yeah. I got too excited.
老友记  第五季  第22集  眼病难医
Friends  S05E22  The One With Joey's Big Break
主演: 珍妮佛·安妮斯顿
主演: 寇妮·考克斯
主演: 丽莎·库卓
主演: 麦特·勒布兰
主演: 马修·派瑞
主演: 大卫·修蒙
先走了  我要带班去公园
All right, I gotta go. I'm taking Ben to the park.
帮我亲下他  好  再见
Oh, give him a kiss for me. All right. Bye.
再见  稍后见
Bye. Bye. Later.
很抱歉让你们夹在中间尴尬
I am so sorry you got caught in the middle of that.
我也不是故意这么夸张  但我真的很生他的气
I didn't mean to be so out there, but I am furious with him.
别激动
Calm down?
我在克制  但一想到那个人我就有气
I'm trying, but, man, that guy can push my buttons.
你干嘛那么气他
Why are you so mad at him?
我不想谈  好吗  只是
Look, I don't wanna talk about it, okay? Well, it seems like...
你想榜上有名  就继续说啊
You wanna be on my list too? Keep talking.
对了  谁有看到我的黑名单
Has anyone seen my list, by the way?
没看到  长什么样子
Uh, no. What's it look like?
就是张纸  上头写了" 罗斯"  了解
Um, a piece of paper and it says "Ross."  I see.
我刚和伊斯特讲完电话  你们猜怎么了
Hey. I just got off the phone with Estelle. and guess what.
我要当电影主角了
I got the lead in a movie.
你要演电影主角  太厉害了  是什么电影
You got the lead in a movie? That's amazing! What's the movie about?
片名是《极限速度》  超酷的
Oh, it's called Shutterspeed. It's really cool.
我在地铁遇见一个女孩  一天之内坠入情网
Yeah, um, I meet this girl in the subway and we fall in love in, like, a day, right?
后来她消失无影无踪  但我找出了她住在哪里
And then she disappears. But I find out where she lives.
到那之后  一个老太太出来开门  我问她 "贝丝在哪里"
And when I get there, this old lady answers the door. I say, "Where's Betsy?"
她说 "贝丝已经过世十年了"
Right? And she says, "Betsy's been dead 10 years."
喔  毛骨悚然
Ooh. Chilling.
最棒的部分是  拍片地点在赌城外的沙漠
Oh, and the best part is we're filming in the desert outside of Vegas.
兄弟  你知道那是啥意思  对  我知道那是啥意思
You know what that means, buddy. Yeah, I know that means buddy
开车杀过去  我们可以租车  我周二以前到那里就行了
Road trip. Yeah, we can rent a car. I just have to be there by Tuesday.
等等  我祖母过世了
Oh, wait. My grandmother's dead.
菲比   我们也可以聊聊那件事
Well, uh, we can talk about that too, Pheebs.
不  不  我是说她的计程车
No, no, her cab.
她八成用不到了  你们可以开去赌城
She probably won't be using it. You could drive it to Las Vegas.
好啊  菲比  谢了
All right. Thanks, Pheebs.
那我的工作怎么办
What are we gonna do about my job?
别去了  好啊  太棒了  上路了
Oh, uh, not go. All right, great. Road trip, baby.
你没意见吧
Is this okay with you?
钱德  你不用征求我的允许
Chandler, you don't have to ask for my permission.
我让你去  谢谢
You can go. Thank you.
瑞秋  快点  要去看眼科了
Hey, Rach, come on, We're gonna be late for the eye doctor appointment
好啦  早去早解脱
All right. Let's get this over with. Ugh.
喔
Oh, no.
糟糕  我真是笨手笨脚的
Look what I did.
搞得一团乱  我得先来清理一下
I mean, look at this mess.I mean, we're gonna probably have to clean this up, you know?
看诊时间得要重约了
I mean, we're gonna have to reschedule.
若你认为这点脏乱会困扰我  那你就错了
If you thought that this mess was gonna bother me, you are wrong.
我们走吧  眨眼姑娘
All right, let's go, Blinky.
钱德
Chandler.
（中央咖啡厅）
乔伊  你怎么了
Oh, hey, Joey. What's up?
我无法决定走哪条路去赌城
I can't decide which route to take to Vegas.
嘿  你去过不少地方吧  对  见过世面
Hey, you've traveled a lot, right? Yeah, I've been around. Okay.
那我该选哪一条  北线还是南线
So which route should I take? The northern route or the southern route?
走北线途经伊利诺州  有个男人会用蜜峰当胡子
Ooh, if you take the north route, there's a man in Illinois with a beard of bees.
太棒了  问题解决
Great. Problem solved.
但是走南线的话  可以看会玩井字游戏的鸡
But on the southern route, there's a chicken that plays tic-tac-toe.
又回到原点了
Well, back to square one.
我知道有个方法能让你做决定
Oh, I know a way that you can decide.
我会问你一连串的问题  你回答得越快越好
All right, I'm gonna ask you a series of questions and you answer as quickly as you can.
好
Yes.
很好  不过先别急
Good. But wait.
开始了  你先放轻松
Here we go. Now I want you to relax.
深呼吸一口气
Take a deep breath.
心里不要想事情
Clear your mind.
花生酱和蛋白  你喜欢哪个  花生酱
Which do you like better peanut butter or egg whites? Peanut butter.
消防员和游泳选手  你比较想当哪一个
Which would you rather be a fireman or a swimmer?
游泳选手
Swimmer.
摩妮卡和瑞秋  你比较想跟谁上床
Who would you rather sleep with Monica or Rachel?
摩妮卡
Monica.
我一直都以为会是瑞秋呢
I always thought it'd be Rachel.
不要想事情  不要想
No thinking, no thinking.
领带或领巾  领巾
Tie or ascot? Ascot.
南线或北线  北线
North route or south route? North.
答案出现  厉害吧
Bam, there you go. Huh? Wow.
不可思议  蜜峰胡  我来了
That was incredible. Beard of bees here I come.
嘿  这家伙又来了
Hey. Oh, this guy again.
你好吗
Hey, what's up?
嗯  没什么  今晚想看电影吗
Uh, not much. You guys wanna see a movie tonight?
好啊  你要看什么
Sure. What do you wanna see?
不知道
I don't know. Um...
我知道我们要如何决定  菲比  让他见识见识你的游戏
I know how we can decide. Phoebe, show him your game.
免了  多谢
Um, no, thank you.
她是怎么了
What's with her?
不知道  但我知道怎么决定了
I don't know. But I know how we can decide.
我问你问题  你要很快回答  好
Okay, I'm gonna ask you questions and you answer real quick, okay?
动作片或喜剧  你比较喜欢哪一个
What do you like better action or comedy?
动作片
Action.
摩妮卡和瑞秋  你比较想跟谁上床
Who would you rather sleep with, Monica or Rachel?
老兄  你真变态
Dude, you are sick.
抱歉  我忘了你迷恋过瑞秋
Oh. I'm sorry. I forgot you had that whole Rachel thing.
天啊  这是干嘛的
Oh, my God. What does that thing do?
这是眼球摘除机
Uh, that's an eye removal machine.
好了  我要走了  开玩笑的啦
All right, I'm out of here. I'm kidding. I'm kidding.
瑞秋  我是米勒医生  摩妮卡说你有点点紧张
Hi, Rachel, I'm Dr. Miller.Monica told me you were a little nervous,
不过别担心  不会有事的
but don't worry everything's gonna be just fine.
那就结束了  还差点  我们要先开始
So we're done then. Almost, but first we gotta start.
这是青光眼测试
This is the glaucoma test.  Uh-huh.
请坐
Sit down.
好吧
Okay.
把脸颊放在这里
Put your chin here.
好  眼睛会有风吹的成觉
Now, you'll feel a small puff of air in each eye.
什么
Uh, a what?
点点的风啦  你快点
A small puff of air. Now, come on.
来了  好
Here we go. All right.
一  二  三
One, two, three.
抱歉  好吧
I'm sorry. All right.
我这次不会动
Ha, ha, I'm gonna stay in here this time. Okay.
好了吗
Ready? Uh-huh.
一  二  抱歉
One, two... I'm sorry.
我来抓她头好了  好
Y'know what, I'm gonna hold her head.
不用了  好
That's okay. Okay.
一  二  对不起
One two... Oh! I'm sorry.
你还年轻  应该没有青光眼
You know what? You're young. You probably don't have glaucoma.
太好了  很高兴认识您
Great!! It was very, very nice to meet you, sir.
嘿  你在干嘛  你疯了不成
Ow! Hey, What are you doing?! Are you crazy?
好   你的左眼有些微感染
Okay. You got a small, minor infection in that left eye.
这眼药水一天点三次  连续一周你就宛如新生了
I want you to take these drops three times a day and you'll be as good as new.
我不把任何东西放进眼睛里
Yeah, no, I don't-I don't put things in my eye.
那好吧  三个月后再见
Okay then. I guess we'll see you back here in three months.
太棒了  到时候我帮你装上假眼
Great. And I'll fit you for a glass eye.
好啦  把那死眼药水给我
Okay, just give me the damn drops.
米勒医生
Dr. Miller?
P E C F D
P-E-C-F-D.
摩妮卡  棒极了
Very good, Monica.
你知道奖品放在哪里  我当然知道
You know where they are. I sure do.
你没有
And you don't get one.
告诉你  那眼药水实在是太神奇了  我的眼睛百分之百好了
Y'know, I-I gotta tell ya, those eye drops are a miracle. My eye is a 100% better.
眼药水还放在我的外套里 可恶
They're still in my coat. Damn.
准备好上路了没有  好了  不过那边会有多冷
Hey. Hey, you ready to go? Yeah, Listen, how cold is it gonna be there?
我要带外套  还是带这些毛衣就够了
Do I need a coat or will all these sweater vests be enough?
怎么了  我爱你
What? I love you.
真希望罗斯也能一起去  我一定会很想念他的
Man, I wish Ross was coming with us. Y'know? I'm gonna miss him.
真是多谢你了  我才刚把那个混蛋给忘掉
Thanks a lot. I just got that jerk out of my mind.
我们住哪里  电影公司招待的饭店大套房
Hey, so where are we staying? Is the movie putting us up in a big hotel suite?
不算是  这是独立制片的电影  没有太多预算
Uh, no, not really. It's an independent film. y'know? So we don't have a real big budget.
我想我住你房间好了
I figured I'd just stay in your room.
了解  但等你拿到酬劳之后  你会请我住饭店大套房吧
I see, but once you get your first paycheck, you'll be springing a big hotel suite, right?
主演电影的片酬  一定不少吧
Lead in the movie, they must be paying you a lot.
是啊  我算给你听
Oh, yeah. Check this out.
《极限速度》每赚一块钱  乔伊就能分到百分之一
For every dollar Shutterspeed makes one penny of it goes right in Joey's pocket.
所以电影赚钱  你才有钱拿
So you don't get paid unless the movie makes money?
你不知道这电影的情节吗
Did you not hear the plot of the movie?
"贝丝已经过世十年了"
"She's been dead for 10 years."
我就快变成百万富翁了
I'm gonna be a millionaire.
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
我只是要来跟你们说个再见
I just wanted to say goodbye to you guys.
顺便托你们帮我下个注
And to see if maybe you guys will place a little bet for me.
20美元押黑色15号
Twenty bucks on black 15.
没问题  好
You got it. All right.
再见  再见  再见
All right. Bye-bye, now.Bye, you guys.
我去车子那里替你送行  好
I'm gonna say goodbye at the car. Okay.
谁要去车子那里替我送行
Anybody wanna say goodbye to me at the car?
我可以替你送行  只要你不介意我眼睛化脓
Oh, honey, I'll say goodbye to you at the car if you don't mind the pus.
再见
See you.
等等  化脓是好现象  表示快要好了
But wait a minute. The pus is good. It means it's healing.
菲比  你在看什么
Hey, Pheebs. What you reading?
菲比
Pheebs?
哈罗
Hello?
菲比
Phoebe?
菲比别闹了啦
Phoe-Phoebe! Come on.
抱歉  我不知道你在这里
Oh, I'm sorry, I didn't see you there.
菲比  你在生我的气吗
Pheebs, are you mad at me or something?
我做了什么让你生气的事
'Cause if are please, tell me what it is I did!
你不知道  我也帮不了你  我是不知道啊
Well, if you don't know, I can't help you. Well, I don't know.
那我也无能为力了
Well, I can't help you.
不管是什么事  我都非常抱歉
Okay, well, whatever it is, I am very, very sorry. Okay?
我接受你的道歉
Apology accepted.
好吧
Okay.
那我们没事了
So we're, we're good? Uh-huh.
好吧
All right.
那晚点见了  好吧  拜拜  大屁股
I'll uh, I'll see you later, okay? okay? Bye, fat ass
够了
All right.
菲比  你快点说  我做了什么让你这么不爽
Phoebe now come on!  will you please tell me what it is that made you so mad at me?
我不知道  我不记得了
I don't know. I don't remember.
既然忘了  那能不能算了
Well, if you can't remember, can't we just forget about this?
不行  我生你的气  这很确定
Oh, no. I am mad at you. I know that much.
但我很抱歉骂你大屁股  因为你的小屁屁很可爱
But I am sorry about the "fat ass" thing because you actually have a very sweet little heinie.
天啊  我开得好累  你得随时准备接手
Man, I'm getting pretty tired. You're might have to take over soon.
我们才上路半小时
We've been driving for a half-hour.
而且你都没在看路
And you haven't looked at the road once.
别担心  路就是路嘛
Don't worry. It's out there.
我想我该吃午饭了 是啊
I think I just need lunch. Yeah.
你要吃吗  我请客
You wanna eat? My treat.
那不是罗斯的钱吗
Isn't that Ross' money?
是啊  好吧  罗斯请客
Yeah, okay. Ross' treat.
你想吃什么  我不知道
Where do you wanna eat? I don't know.
我知道要怎么决定了
Oh, hey, I know how we can decide.
我问你一堆问题  你得很快回答
All right, uh, I'm gonna ask you questions.and then you have to answer real fast, okay?
不要想事情  什么都不要想  好
So, uh, clear your mind. Clear it right out. Clear it out.Okay.
你宁愿太湿或太干  太干
Would you rather be too wet or too dry? Too dry.
你相不相信有鬼  不相信
Do you believe in ghosts?  yes or no?  No.
这电影会让我翻身吗  不会
Is this movie gonna be my big break? No.
什么  会
What? Yes.
你刚才说不会
Dude, you said no.
我也说了会啊
I also said yes.
你不觉得我这次会翻身  对
You don't think this is gonna be a big break for me? No! Ahhh!!!
岂有此理
I don't believe this.
乔伊  我只是不要你期望太高
Look, Joe, I just, I just don't want you to get your hopes up too high.
你在胡说什么  我是电影主角啊
What are you talking about? I'm the lead in a movie.
那他们还不付你片酬
They're not even paying you.
这电影听来跟幌子一样
This doesn't even sound like a real movie.
我不需要听这种话  搞不懂你干嘛泄我的气
Y'know what? I don't need this! Okay? I don't know why you're dumping all over my big break.
乔伊  我不认为你这次能翻身
Because, Joe, I don't think this is going to be your big break.
所以你才来这趟   让我觉得自己是窝囊废
Is that why you're on this trip? Huh? To make me feel like a loser?
如果是这样  那我宁愿自己去
'Cause if it is, I'll tell ya, I-I-I'd rather be alone.
你不要我陪你去  你这样我不要也罢
You don't want me on the trip? Not if you're like this.
那好吧  下次你再问那种问题  我骗你就是了
Tell you what,the next time you ask me a question like that, I'll lie.
对  我不要你一起去
Yeah, I don't want you on the trip.
好  无所谓  你停车  我  马上走
All right, fine. Why don't you pull over? I'll get out now.
好啊
Fine.
滚吧  在桥上不能随便就停车
Get out. You're not supposed to stop on a bridge.
滚啦  好啦
Get out. Fine.
等等  桥上没有人行道
Wait. Wait. There's no sidewalk.
对  我一定会死在这里
Yeah. I'm gonna die here.
好  你生我的气  是因为我发胶有怪味
Okay, are you mad at me because my hair gel smells?
不是
No.
你生我的气  是因为我说你写字像小孩
Are you angry with me because I said your handwriting is childlike?
不是  这样才特别啊
No, that made me feel precious.
我知道了  因为他老爱纠正别人文法
Oh, I know. Is it because he's always correcting people's grammar?
什么" WHOM" 个没完
You know, "whom, whom."
有时候是用" WHO" 啦！
Sometimes it's "who."
是吗  有时候是
Yeah? Sometimes it's...
还是你玩西洋棋赢了他  他开始居于劣势就很孩子气
Oh, did you beat him at a board game?He turns into such a baby when he starts to lose.
好  我孩子气
Okay, I'm the baby.
嘿  不要啊
Hey. Stop it
嗨  钱德  你怎么会在这里
Hey. Chandler! What are you doing here?
乔伊在华盛顿大桥上 把我赶下车
Joey kicked me out of the car on the George Washington bridge!
为什么
Why?
不知道  他突然发疯  我们在玩快问快答的游戏
I don't know. He went crazy. Y'know, We were playing that game where you ask a question and you answer it really fast.
没有我在场监督  绝对不能玩那个游戏
Oh, that game should not be played without my supervision.
我不知道他干嘛气成那样
Well, I don't know what made him mad.
我只是说他这次不会翻身
All I said was that, uh, I didn't think this was gonna be his big break...
说这部电影帮不了他
...that this movie wasn't gonna do anything for him...
说这部电影很像是幌子
...and that uh, y'know it didn't sound like a real movie.
好啦  他该把我推下桥才对
Okay, he should've pushed me off the bridge.
你袋子里有什么
What's in the bag?
我猜想你们大家也会对我不爽
Oh, I figured you guys would all be mad at me...
所以我在路边捡了些礼物
...so I got you some gifts that I found on the side of the road.
谁要一条腿的泰迪熊  我要
Who wants the teddy bear with one leg? I do.
来了
Okay.
差远了  好啦  你帮我  我没办法
Not even close. Okay, then y'know what? I need help! I can't do this!
来  我帮你
Okay! All right! Let's do it!
坐下 好
All right. Sit down.
头往后仰  好
All right, put your head back. All right. Yes. Okay.
把眼睛张开  好  张开了
Now, open your eyes. Okay, they are.
我举了几只手指头  四只
How many fingers am I holding up? Four.
天啊  我心里想的也是四只
Oh, my God, I was thinking four.
真的  是啊
Really? Yes.
这样吧   我们先来预演次  好
All right, y'know what? why don't we start with a practice one, okay?
不滴眼药水  太好了
No drops. Great.
数到三   一  二  三
On three. One, two, three.
你害的我沙发枕都湿了
Now my pillow's all wet.
你自己说是预演的
Well, well, you said it was practice!
那你干嘛动  因为我知道你在骗我
Then why did you move? Because I knew you were lying.
好吧  过来  你要干嘛
All right. Come here. Come on. What are you doing?
摩妮卡  天啊  住手
Monica, Stop it! Oh, my God, stop it.
我要  转回来
I am going… I'm going--Turn it over!
我要把眼药水  滴进你眼睛
Aah!I am going to get Get these drops in your eye.
天啊  你的蛮力真大
Oh, my God. You really are freakishly strong.
摩妮卡  住手
Aah! Aah! Monica, stop it!
可恶  滴完了
Damn, it's empty.
如果现在乔伊和钱德走进来  我们就发了
Wow. y'know if Joey and Chandler walked in right now, we could make a fortune.
一定是钱德  乔伊或罗斯
Ooh, that is definitely Chandler, Joey or Ross.
或是瑞秋
Or Rachel.
喂
Hello?
是乔伊
It's Joey.
真高兴你打来  钱德都说了  他很难过
I'm so glad you called. Chandler told me what happened. He's really upset.
等他知道他毛衣的下场  他一定会更难过
Not as upset as he's gonna be when he finds out what I did with his sweater vests.
你把他的毛衣怎么了
What did you do to his sweater vests?
这么说吧  在俄玄俄州  有一伙打扮亮丽的狗
Let's just say there's a well-dressed pack of dogs in Ohio.
摩妮卡  菲比在吗  我有车子的事要问她
Monica, listen, is Phoebe there? I gotta ask her something about the car.
她在  你等等
Yeah, she's here. Hold on a second.
嗨  嗨  菲比
Hey, dude. Hey, Pheebs.
你听我说  座位底下有个木盒滑出来  那是什么
Listen, this wooden box keeps sliding out from under the seat. What is it?
那是我祖母
Oh, that's my grandma.
乔伊  谢谢你  她玩得很愉快
And thanks, Joey. She's having a really great time.
是乔伊吗  是乔伊吗  我要跟他说
Is that Joey? Is that Joey? Let me talk to him.
乔伊  钱德在这儿  不知道你
Joey, Chandler's here. He was wondering if...
我想他零钱正好用完了
Okay, I guess he ran out of change.
他连话都不想跟我说  这样我要怎么跟他道歉
Y'know, He won't even talk to me. How am I gonna apologize to him if he won't even talk to me?
或许你应该寄点东西给他
Maybe you should send him something.
等他到了赌城  就知道你想表达歉意了
So when he gets to Las Vegas, he'll know that you're sorry.
好主意  上哪儿找一堆成人A片呢
That's a good idea. I wonder where I could get a basket of porn?
不行  不能用成人片道歉啦  真的
Oh, no,  don't-don't say I'm sorry with porn! Really?
你应该寄一条烟过去  他可以用来换取保护
You know what you should send him? A carton of cigarettes. 'Cause that why he could trade it for protection.
错了  监狱里才是这样
No. That's prison.
菲比  我知道要怎么找出原因了
Okay, Pheebs. I know how we're gonna figure this out.
好  什么都不要想
Okay. Clear your mind...
想到什么就直接回答
...and answer the first thing that comes into your head.
好了吗
Okay?
你比较喜欢植物还是动物  动物
What do you like better flora or fauna Fauna. Fauna.
你想当赛门还是葛芬柯  葛芬柯
Who would you rather be Simon or Garfunkle? Garfunkel.
你为何生我的气  因为你说我很无趣
Why are you mad at me? You said I was boring. Oh.
我何时说过你无趣了
When did I say you were boring?
天啊  我想起来了  我们下西洋棋那次
Oh, my God, I remember now. We were playing chess.
菲比  我和你没下过西洋棋
Phoebe, you and I have never played chess.
有啦  记得冰冻湖那次吗  我们玩西洋棋  你说我很无趣
Oh, come on! Yes, remember that time on the frozen lake? We were playing chess, you said I was boring,
然后你脱下面具  变成了卡麦蓉狄亚
and then you took off your energy mask and you were Cameron Diaz!.
好吧  这有可能是梦境
Okay, there's a chance this may have been a dream.
嘿  史丹利  嘿
Hey. Stanley. Hey.
你的主角来了  咱们开工吧
Your leading man is here. Let's get to work.
计划有些改变   我们停拍了
Um, slight change of plans. We've shut down.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
钱的原因吧  我们没钱
It's a money thing. We don't have any.
你在开玩笑吧  不是
Ha, ha. You're kidding, right? No.
什么
What?
这或许只是暂时的
It's probably just temporary.
我们希望能快点筹到资金  你先撑一下
We're hoping to get more money soon, so if you could just, uh, hang out.
撑一下  要撑多久
Hang out? How long?
不知道  一周  或许两个星期吧
I don't know. A week. Maybe two.
资金会出现的  大家都爱投资拍片
The money'll turn up. People always wanna invest in movies.
你该不会是有钱人吧  我不是
Hey, you're not rich, are you? No.
问一下也无妨
Worth a shot.
乔伊  让我知道你在哪儿落脚
Well, Joey, let me know where you're staying, okay?
老兄  你是乔伊崔比亚尼吗  我是
Hey, pal. Are you Joey Tribbiani? Yeah.
这是有人留给你的  谢了
These got left for you. Thanks.
" 恭喜你翻身了"
"Congratulations on your big break."
喂
Hello?
摩妮卡  我是乔伊
Monica, it's Joey.
乔伊  你当了大明星还记得我
Hey, Joey.Aw, you remember me even though you're a big star.
得了吧   忘记你也要好几年
Aw, come on. It'll be years before I forget you.
乔伊  拍片现场是什么样子
Joey, what's it like on a movie set, huh?
你有自己的更衣室吗  有专属的私人座椅吗
Do you have a dressing room? Do you have a chair with your name on it?
有啊  一切都在进行当中
Uh, yeah, yeah, I got all that going on.
你一定要跟钱德说  他完完全全看走眼了
Listen, uh, make sure you tell Chandler he couldn't have been more wrong.
摩妮卡  我得挂了  我的寿司送来了
Uh-oh, I gotta go, Monica. My, uh, sushi's here.
抱歉  多谢你们等我  没关系
Sorry about that. Thanks for waiting. Okay.
大家笑一个  好了  多谢
Everybody smile. Okay. Thanks a lot.
希望你们在凯萨住得愉快  祝福你们" 罗马" 精神
Enjoy your stay at Caesar's. We hope it's toga-rific.
杀了我  杀了我吧
Ugh. Kill me. Kill me now.
瑞秋  《电视指南》递给我好吗  好啊
Hey, Rach, can you pass me the TV Guide?  Yeah.
上
Go!
干嘛
What are you doing?
住手  天啊
Get off! Oh, my God!
睁开  好了
Hold it open. Okay. Aah!
三  四个小时后再见
We'll see you in about three or four hours.